u-exchange.com 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for U-Exchange.com**

At U-Exchange.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit U-Exchange.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This includes  the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums and your member homepage.

We also use third party advertisements on U-Exchange.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this will affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or member accounts.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Photos may be used periodically as examples of items for trade throughout the website and in advertising. Your personal information such as e-mail, phone number, last name and street address will _not_ be displayed to visitors.
